[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Rocky Balboas daytime occupation in the 1976 movie Rocky?", "correct_answer": "Debt collector", "incorrect_answers": ["Taxi driver", "Salesman", "Electrician"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of these major subtopics is not part of classical mechanics.", "correct_answer": "Kinetic theory", "incorrect_answers": ["Chaos theory", "Lagrangian mechanics", "Fluid dynamics"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Topeka is the capital city of which U.S. state?", "correct_answer": "Kansas", "incorrect_answers": ["Arkansas", "Missouri", "Colorado"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This food is rich in omega \u2013 3 fatty acids, magnesium and potassium.", "correct_answer": "Oatmeal", "incorrect_answers": ["Salmon", "Dark Chocolate", "Berries"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie, Casablanca, the Bulgarian couple tell Louis that they will be at his office at 6:00 AM to make arrangements for their exit visas. What is Louis reply?", "correct_answer": "Ill be there at 10.", "incorrect_answers": ["Ill be there, waiting on you.", "Ill be there. Just knock.", "Take your time. The planes are always late."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Feijohada has been consumed for centuries in this country. It is a stew made of black beans and pork.", "correct_answer": "Brazil", "incorrect_answers": ["Spain", "Mexico", "Portugal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the longest bone in the body.", "correct_answer": "Femur", "incorrect_answers": ["Fibula", "Tibia", "Humerus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What name does the little girl in the 2004 movie Man on Fire give to her favorite teddy bear?", "correct_answer": "Creasy", "incorrect_answers": ["W", "Sam", "Johnny"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Joe Barry Carroll was drafted by the Golden Gate Warriors in 1980. He was the first choice in that draft. Who did they give up to get him?", "correct_answer": "Robert Parrish and Kevin McHale", "incorrect_answers": ["Dennis Rodman and John Paxson", "Charles Barkley and Tim McCormick", "Michael Jordan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these countries is a major producer of gold?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["South Africa", "China", "United States"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did Mary Phelps Jacobs create the first modern bra after getting mad at her hard bodice? She covered its bones with silk handkerchief and attached it with a couple of cords.", "correct_answer": "1913", "incorrect_answers": ["1912", "1920", "1925"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mitchell, Jardine, Staaten, Flinders, Leichhardt, and Nicholson are just few of the rivers in this country.", "correct_answer": "Australia", "incorrect_answers": ["Indonesia", "Papua New Guinea", "New Zealand"]}]